# LE DUONG HIEN THONG (MICHAEL)

# **Summary**

A Fullstack Web Developer with a background in quality assurance and quality control. I love being innovative and have the ability in designing user interfaces, testing codes and constructing databases and servers to develop intriguing and user-friendly web application. My passion have led me to completed my Fullstack Web Development Diploma through Lighthouse Labs. I love creating projects that require extensive research analysis with contents that intersect between field of science and programming.

# **Employment**

# **Quality Control - Chemist**

Apotex Inc.

Jan. 2021 to Aug. 2021 North York, ON

- Analyzed 100+ drug samples and documented all data obtained from testing to complete daily report summaries.
- Collaborated with internal chemists to ensure compliance with good manufacturing practices, and good laboratory practices, as well as the Ontario Occupational Health and Safety Act.

# **Cleaning Validation Coordinator**

Apotex Inc.

Sept. 2019 to Dec. 2019 North York, ON

- Assisted in gradient study projects and provided troubleshooting assistance for remedial and corrective actions in the case of unacceptable validation results by analyzing inventory data using SAP and LIMS.
- Conducted product risk assessments to categorize newly developed products by analyzing products' physical, chemical properties, and their formulation details.

# **Projects**

#### **BAYSTREETBETS**

Aug. 2022 to Current

A stock trading platform. In additional to features that allow user to keep track of their stocks and portfolios, BayStreetBets's unique feature is the ability to allow users to compete with their peers in a stock trading competition, crowning the one that earn the most.

Front end: HTML, SCSS, React

Back-end: Node, Express, PostgreSQL, React-router

Test: Jest, Cypress

**PINNET** 

July 2022 to July 2022

An address notebook. Pinnet offers users the ability to pin and save their favorite place to eat or hangout by creating their own sharable address list.

Front end: HTML, SCSS, EJS

Back-end: Node, Express, PostgreSQL

Test: Mocha & Chai

#### **SCHEDULER**

July 2022 to July 2022

An appointment scheduler. Scheduler allows users to book interviews appointment with a list of interviewers available on the selected day.

Front end: HTML, SCSS, React

Back-end: Node, Express, PostgreSQL

Test: Jest, Storybook, Cypress

**JUNGLE** Aug. 2022 to Aug. 2022

A mini e-commerce. Built with Ruby on Rails, the application allows visitors to view, purchase, and products.

**Front end:** Ruby, Bootstrap CSS **Back-end:** Rails, StripAPI, PostgreSQL

Test: Cypress

# Contact

★ htleduong529@gmail.com

**4** 647-395-5029

▼ Toronto, Ontario

in michael-leduong

n diavolosz

# Skills

## LANGUEGE

JavaScript

HTML

CSS

SCSS

Ruby

#### **FRAMEWORKS**

Node.js

React.js

jQuery

Ruby on Rails

### **TEST**

Mocha & Chai

Jest

Cypress

Storybook

### **DATABASE**

SQL (POSTgreSQL)

## SERVER

Express.js

# **Education**

## **Lighthouse Lab**

May 2022 to Aug. 2022

Diploma Full-Stack Web Development

### **University of Waterloo**

Sept. 2019 to Apr. 2022

B.S. Bachelor of Biochemistry -

Biotechnology Specialization